EZEUGWU ANTHONY CHUKWUMA

| 63 Sijuwola Street, Ago Palace way, Okota Lagos. Oshodi/Isolo 100001 || 07083225145 |
| chukwumaanthony97@gmail.com || Nationality: Nigerian || LinkedIn : www.linkedin.com/in/anthony-ezeugwu-b6286529b |
| PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY |

I am a hardworking and motivated Software Engineer who has acquired extensive knowledge in the field through the study of Computer Science at degree level and work experience in tech firms. I have strengthened my skills in frontend web development with experience involving projects. Moreover, I have contributed immensely to improve my skills on a daily basis resulting to increased performance and productivity. |
| WORK HISTORY |

UNIFIED PAYMENT - Victoria Island, Lagos

- I continue to enhance UI functionalities within the company's codebase, similar to my previous experience.
- I collaborated closely with our ASP.NET backend team, diving deep into API specifications to craft robust data communication solutions. Thorough texting ensures our integrated APIs are not just reliable but also high-performing, guaranteeing efficiency across our applications.
- I work closely with my team to design and build the company's applications, ensuring they have user-friendly and visually appealing interfaces.
- I also worked on new projects alongside UI/UX designers and the backend developers building user friendly applications.

Junior Software Developer

Junior Software Developer

December 2022 - January 2024

February 2024 - Date

TM30 Global Limited - Onikan, Lagos

- Modified existing UI functionalities within the company's codebase
- Actively collaborated with team members to architect and develop client applications. This
 involved working closely with designers to implement responsive and visually appealing user
 interfaces.
- Worked closely with backend developers to understand API specifications, implemented robust solutions for data communication and conducted thorough testing to guarantee the reliability and efficiency of the integrated API.

Internship

September 2022 – Nov 2022

New Horizon – Lagos, Festac

- Worked with senior colleagues in integrating API
- · Built responsive and user-friendly interfaces with html, css and tailwind

TECHNOLOGY AND SKILLS -

React JS Communication

HTML and CSS Creativity

API integration Teamwork

Github Time Management

MYSQL Javascript

_____ EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science - Computer Science October 2018 – August, 2022

Caleb University - Lagos State

Command Secondary School - Apata, Ibadan 2012 – 2018

Golden Bunch Nursery and primary School - Okota Lagos 2003 – 2012